Imagine being a white dude who makes a living suing black women
so that they can't help other women of color start small businesses
because that would be racist against white people.
Meet Edward Bloom.
He's the legal strategist that brought a lawsuit to the Supreme Court in June
that ended affirmative action in colleges, and he's not done.
In total, he's brought eight cases to the Supreme Court since the 1990s,
but a recent suit jumps out.
He's suing Fearless Fund, a small venture capital fund founded by black women
to help other women of color start businesses.
Bloom is arguing that the Civil Rights Act of 1866, the year after the Civil War ended,
states that white people should have access to a fund specifically made for minority entrepreneurs
or else it's racist.
And he's winning.
In October, a court blocked Fearless Fund's grant program.
So now the fund is fighting this racist bullshit.
I am on here today because we are launching our Fearless Freedom campaign.
Many of you guys know that we are in the midst of a historical battle.
Yes, a court case that is determining whether people like me and you can provide funding to women of color.
What the fuck is wrong with these people?
How do you as a man wake up hard in the morning knowing that you're making money
by going out and telling people in marginalized communities that they can't do what they want with their money?
Bloom has also sued three law firms this fall because their DEI programs exclude white people.
One has already changed their program while an unrelated firm that wasn't being sued proactively changed theirs in fear of Bloom.
Make no mistake, these are the same people that are out there saying that critical race theory is racist against white people.
We live in a time when it's possible to connect with people all over the world instantaneously to learn about their cultures,
to enjoy their foods and their music, and try to understand who they are.
And we'd rather spend it fucking with them.
There's a lot of deserved emphasis right now on the overturning of Roe v. Wade,
and we need to continue to discuss and fight against that.
But these courts are busy right now due to the MAGA legacy.
And as we see, they're only getting busier.
It's really just sad.
Like, do something good with your life.
Why would this be what you devote your time to?
What is wrong with you?